Nouman Ejaz

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

noumanejaz6967@gmail.com 🔀

+923115946967

Islamabad, Pakistan 💡

www.linkedin.com/in/noumanejaz in

SUMMARY

My eagerness toward gaining knowledge about advancements and innovations in emerging technologies inspired me to choose computer sciences as a field of study and career. BS degree provided me the foundational knowledge. Being a software engineer and working on freelance projects helped me to gain hands-on experience in developing websites using different web technologies and CMS (i.e WordPress, etc). Positive attitudes, a pro-active approach towards personal development, analytical and problem-solving skills are my assets, which enabled me to achieve success and are my key resources to grow professionally.

SKILLS

WordPress	jQuery	
HTML	Javascript	
Bootstrap	C++	
CSS	Php	• • • • •
WebFlow		

EXPERIENCE

WordPress Developer

Ropstam Solutions Inc. May 2022 - Present

Software Engineer

Unicorn Technologies Sep 2018 - Apr 2022

WordPress Developer (Intern)

Unicorn Technologies Jul 2018 - Aug 2018

PROJECTS

Unicorn Technologies

Ex Company Website Redesign Feb 2022 - Mar 2022 https://unicorntechno.com/

Luca

Reading Platform / Animations: https://luca.ai/

Happy Buddies

An Ecommerce Website For Dog Breed https://happybuddies.org/

Styleline Interiors

Business Website related to Interior Designing https://stylelineinteriors.com/

Vitae Investments

Business Website: http://vitaeinvestments.no/

Bruhn Crossing

Business Website: https://bruhncrossing.ca/

View all Projects in the Google Doc by Clicking Below Link

https://bit.ly/3I4ucH8

EDUCATION Bachelor of Computer Science - BS(CS)

COMSATS University Islamabad, Attock Campus Feb 2016 - Jan 2020

CGPA: 3.21/4.00

CERTIFICATION

Participated In Speed Programing Competition

FAST University Lahore

Participated in a national level event Geek For Geeks'18

Participated In Speed Programing Competition

COMSTAS University Islamabad, Attock Campus Participated in a national level event NatQuals'18

Participated In Speed Programing Competition

COMSTAS University Islamabad, Attock Campus Participated in a national level event COMBITS'17

AWARDS

Ambassador From CUI Attock Campus in Visio Spark 2019

COMSTAS University Islamabad, Wah Campus 2019-11-23

I was selected twice as an ambassador by COMSATS University Islamabad, Attock campus in Visio Spark 2018 & 2019. Visio Spark is a national level event held every year at COMSATS University Islamabad Wah Campus.

REFERRAL

Global Supply Chain Professional - WETHEBRANDS

Phone: +92 342 5303613

Email: zeeshan@we-the-brands.com **Website**: https://we-the-brands.com/